http://www.gulfstreampark.com/info/privacy-policy

Your privacy is important to us. PLEASE READ
Gulfstream Park has created this electronic privacy statement in order to demonstrate our firm commitment to privacy. We believe that strong electronic privacy is crucial for the ongoing success of the Internet as a service, commercial, and entertainment medium. The following discloses our electronic information gathering and dissemination practices for our racetrack facility and our website: www.gulfstreampark.com
COLLECTION AND USE OF PERSONAL INFORMATION
We may collect the following personal information from you: your first and last name, your email address, driver’s license number, mailing address, telephone number and demographic information. You may opt-out of receiving communications from us by following the instructions in the “Choice/Opt-Out” Section below.
We use information about you for monitoring and improving our internal operations, to properly perform any services you have requested, to comply with applicable laws and regulations, to improve the experience of users on our website, for marketing and promotional purposes, and to direct important notices and information to you including in respect of events conducted at our facility. Gulfstream Park does not collect personal information about you except when you provide it to Gulfstream Park on a voluntary basis.
Occasionally we run surveys, newsletters, contests or promotions for additional products and services that we market for ourselves, for affiliates or for third parties (“General Solicitations”). You will be periodically contacted in respect of such General Solicitations which we reasonably believe may be of interest to you or be useful to you, either directly by us or by our corporate parent, The Stronach Group. If you wish to no longer receive General Solicitations from us, you have the option to opt out of receiving such emails by following the instructions in the “Choice/Opt-Out” Section below.
LINKS AND PUBLIC FORUMS
Our website may contain links to other websites. Our website is not responsible or liable for the privacy practices or content of such other websites.
Please be aware than any information, personal or otherwise, that you disclose online in a message board or chat room makes that information public information. You should exercise caution when deciding to disclose your personal information online. Gulfstream Park is not responsible for personally identifiable information posted on such public forums.
USE OF COOKIES
A cookie is a small data file that is sent to your browser from a web server and stored on your computer’s hard drive. Cookies do not damage your system or impair its functioning in any way. Gulfstream Park may use cookies to tailor and enhance your experience at its website, to show you content that you might be interested in, to display content according to your preferences and to track website traffic patterns. Cookies do not contain any personal identifying information and cannot read data off your hard disk.
POLICY CHANGES
Gulfstream Park has the right to modify this privacy policy from time to time and shall make, at its sole discretion, such changes or modifications as it deems appropriate.
SECURITY
Our website has security measures in place to protect the loss, misuse and alteration of the personal information under our control. All data is kept on secure database servers.
All data entry is done via a secure interface that provides no export facility. Please be advised, however, that the Internet and other networking communication mediums are not secure, unless specified as such, and may be subject to interception or loss which is beyond the control of Gulfstream Park. Also be advised that the security, integrity and privacy of any and all information and data exchanged between you and Gulfstream Park on this website cannot be guaranteed.
TEXT SERVICES
Standard data/text message charges may apply. All those that “opt in” via a text message may be contacted by Gulfstream Park in the future. Gulfstream Park will limit contact by two (2) text messages per month (this does not include “opt in” or “keyword” text messages). You automatically “opt in” if you text a keyword to Gulfstream Park’s short code ‘72727’. Gulfstream Park will not divulge this information to any other party, meaning messages will only be sent by Gulfstream Park. At anytime a customer may “opt out” of Gulfstream Park’s text messages by replying STOP to 72727 or by e-mailingcontact@gulfstreampark.com including your phone number and that you would like to stop receiving these messages. Gulfstream Park is not liable for any charges applied by your service.
CONFIDENTIALITY AND SHARING OF INFORMATION
We will keep your personal information and will not share, sell or rent such information to unaffiliated third parties, unless such disclosure is necessary to, (a) comply with a court order or other legal process, or (b) protect our rights or property.
CHOICE/OPT-OUT
You are allowed at any time to opt out of our email list entirely, out of receiving all General Solicitations, or out of only receiving any third party General Solicitations by either clicking on the opt-out selection on any email we send or by sending an email to Reply@gulfstreampark.com with the subject, “Opt Me Out”. All such requests are honored promptly, usually within 24-48 hours.
ACCESS TO INFORMATION
If you desire access to your own personal information, to correct existing personal information or to remove your personal information, please contact us by writing to the following: Marketing Department, Gulfstream Park, Marketing Department, 901 S. Federal Highway, Hallandale Beach, Fl 33010. You may change your information at any time and as often as necessary. If you request removal or deletion of your personal information, you acknowledge that residual information may continue to reside in our records and back-up files.
CONTACTING US
If you have any question about this privacy statement, the practices of this website or your dealings with this website, you can contact us electronically at reply@gulfstreampark.com or by writing to:
Gulfstream Park
Marketing Department
901 S. Federal Highway
Hallandale Beach, Fl 33010
Plan Your Visit
About Gulfstream Park
Accommodations
Admission & Parking
